export const QuestionData = [
    {
        question: " Question 1?",
        options: ["Option A", "Option B", "Option C", "Option D"],
        answer: 0 // Index of the correct option (0 for Option A)
    },
    {
        question: " Question 2?",
        options: ["Option A", "Option B", "Option C", "Option D"],
        answer: 1 // Index of the correct option (1 for Option B)
    },
    {
        question: " Question 3?",
        options: ["Option A", "Option B", "Option C", "Option D"],
        answer: 2 // Index of the correct option (2 for Option C)
    },
    {
        question: " Question 4?",
        options: ["Option A", "Option B", "Option C", "Option D"],
        answer: 3 // Index of the correct option (3 for Option D)
    },
    {
        question: "Question 5?",
        options: ["Option A", "Option B", "Option C", "Option D"],
        answer: 0 // Index of the correct option (0 for Option A)
    },
    {
        question: " Question 6?",
        options: ["Option A", "Option B", "Option C", "Option D"],
        answer: 1 // Index of the correct option (1 for Option B)
    },
    {
        question: " Question 7?",
        options: ["Option A", "Option B", "Option C", "Option D"],
        answer: 2 // Index of the correct option (2 for Option C)
    },
    {
        question: " Question 8?",
        options: ["Option A", "Option B", "Option C", "Option D"],
        answer: 3 // Index of the correct option (3 for Option D)
    },
    {
        question: " Question 9?",
        options: ["Option A", "Option B", "Option C", "Option D"],
        answer: 0 // Index of the correct option (0 for Option A)
    },
    {
        question: " Question 10?",
        options: ["Option A", "Option B", "Option C", "Option D"],
        answer: 1 // Index of the correct option (1 for Option B)
    }
];
